<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Meldezettel Graz</string>

    <string name="impressum">This App was created in the course of the lecutre „Softwareengineering Basic“ as a student project under the instruction of professor Robert Ladstätter.\n\n
        “Meldezettel Graz” is aiming to allow a user to fill out a document that was inspired by the Grazer Meldezettel and to save the document. \nAdditionally, it is possible to create a userprofil and to search for existing residence records as well as to edit them if necessary.\n\n
        Following students were working on this project: \n\n
        Lukas Schneider as Team Leader and creator of the concept. \n\n
        Viktor Ielnikov as Code Owner and creator of the structure design. \n\n
        Vanessa Fortmueller as Leader of Documentation as well as interface testing. \n\n
        Following licence was used: \n
        Professional Placeholder Licence\n\n
        Created 2017\n</string>

    <string name="information">
        1. You are required to apply for a residence registration within 3 (three) days after having moved to a new address, and to cancel your residence registration within 3 (three) days before leaving or after having left your old address.\n\n2. You need the following documents to register:\n\n- Official documents, e.g. passport or birth certificate, stating family name, first name, maiden name, date of birth, place of birth and nationality of the person concerned;\n\n- Non-Austrian citizens (foreigners) always need to present a travel document, e.g. passport;\n\n- if the address, which has been your main residence so far, turns into a “further residence” you have to change your main residence registration before or at the same time when you register your new main residence.\n\n3. No matter who completes the registration form, the person responsible for the registration is always responsible that the information provided is correct. Please make sure that the information provided in your registration form is complete and correct even if it is filled in by the authority.\n\n4. Your main residence is the address to which you have moved with the intention to make it the centre of your life. If this prerequisite is true for more than one address, you have to indicate the address as main residence to which you have the closest relation. The following facts are important to define an address as main residence which is the centre of your life: duration of stay, location of workplace or school, place from where you go to work or school, residence of other family members, in particular of minor family members, and the place where you work, go to school or day care, posts in public or private corporations. Your main residence is essential for registration in the federal voters’ register and for several other official tasks such as car registration, gun permits, and welfare assistance.\n\n5. Please keep in mind that if you change your main residence or a further residence you might also have to change other documents such as your car registration or gun permit.
    </string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
</resources>
